# CORINNE NAGEL

## MULTIMEDIA DESIGNER

Multimedia Designer with an aptitude for creating concise infographics, captivating illustrations, user-friendly web applications and effective marketing campaign collateral. Experience in video and photo production as well as bringing imagery to life with motion design. Offers a diverse set of in-demand skills with an inspired point of view.



CORINNENAGEL.COM



DENVER, COLORADO



DESIGN@CORINNENAGEL.COM

# SKILLS

ADOBE CREATIVE SUITE
PROFICIENT ON MAC/PC PLATFORMS
ENVIRONMENTAL DESIGN
VIDEO/PHOTOGRAPHY PRODUCTION

ART DIRECTION
WEB DESIGN
MICROSOFT OFFICE
EVENT DESIGN

PRINT DESIGN
VIDEO DESIGN
ILLUSTRATION
INTERACTIVE DESIGN

UI/UX DESIGN MOBILE APP DESIGN INFOGRAPHIC DESIGN SOCIAL GRAPHICS

# EDUCATION

#### BFA IN VISUAL COMMUNICATIONS

Truman State University Kirksville, MO

#### LORENZO DE' MEDICI: THE ITALIAN INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE

Florence, Italy

Study abroad coursework in Painting and Drawing

#### EXPERIENCE

#### HANGAR30

Web Designer

August 2014 - Present

Responsible for design and production within the Hangar30 Marketing Team and collaborates in concepting and executing creative. Projects range from web design to mobile app development as well as video and logo design. Works to create and improve production workflow and partners with other members of marketing, advertising and product teams to create materials and elements that help bring the client's brand to life.

#### **EXPRESS SCRIPTS**

Graphic Designer

July 2013 - July 2014

Produced engaging visual communications for both internal and external audiences. Designed and executed communications materials including print and digital sales collateral, internal training materials, meeting presentations and events graphics. Developed innovative concepts, created compelling design solutions and followed through to final delivery on a wide variety of B2B and B2C marketing projects.

#### **SCOTTRADE**

Multimedia Designer

July 2011 - July 2013

Designed and illustrated original graphics for various departments and was solely responsible for an array of internal and external projects involving web, video, logo and graphic design. Received positive accolades throughout the company for consistently producing innovative concepts.

# SCOTTRADE

Multimedia Designer Intern

June 2010 - August 2010

Handled projects that consisted of Power Point presentation, logo and video design. Provided valuable creative assistance on numerous projects and collaborated with video editors.